Good food. Fine ales. Total Annihilation.
The World's End is a comedy, action, science
fiction film directed by Edgar Wright.
Five friends who reunite in an attempt to top their epic pub crawl from 20 years
earlier unwittingly become humankind's only hope for survival.
Gary King, played by Simon Pegg.
Andrew Knightley, played by Nick Frost.
Steven Prince, played by Paddy Considine.
Oliver Chamberlain, played by Martin Freeman.
Peter Page, played by Eddie Marsan.
Sam Chamberlain, played by Rosamund Pike.
This Is the End is a 2013 American apocalyptic comedy horror film written, directed and
produced by Seth Rogen and Evan Goldberg in their directorial debuts.
It is a feature-length film adaptation of Rogen and Goldberg's 2007 short film Jay and Seth Versus the
Apocalypse, which was directed by Jason Stone, who serves as an executive producer on the film.
Starring James Franco, Jonah Hill, Rogen, Jay Baruchel, Danny McBride, Craig Robinson, Michael Cera and Emma Watson, the
film centers on fictionalized versions of its cast in the wake of a global biblical apocalypse in Los Angeles.
Produced by Mandate Pictures and Rogen and Goldberg's Point Grey Pictures, This Is the End premiered at the Fox Village Theater on June 3, 2013,
before being released theatrically in the United States on June 12, 2013 by Sony Pictures Releasing, via its Columbia Pictures label.
The film received generally positive reviews from critics, who
praised its humor and the six leads' chemistry.
It was also a commercial success, having grossed $127 million
worldwide against a budget of $32–41.9 million.
The film explores themes of addiction, alcoholism,
end of the world, apocalypse, homage.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.